(Raj:)That technique for creating
a new heavy element is inspired.
(Sheldon:)Thank you.
Believe it or not,
(Sheldon:)I just learned
a Chinese research team
(Sheldon:)at the Hubei Institute
for Nuclear Physics
(Sheldon:)ran a test on a cyclotron,
(Sheldon:)and the results
were extremely promising.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, that's incredible.
I know! They called it
the greatest thing
(Sheldon:)since the Communist party.
(Sheldon:)Although I'm pretty sure that the
Communist party made them say that.
(Sheldon:)I like China.
(Sheldon:)See, they know how
to keep people in line.
(Howard:)So, what happens next?
(Sheldon:)More testing,
more success, more fame.
(Sheldon:)But don't worry, I will remain
the same down-to-earth humble Joe
(Sheldon:)-I've always been.
-Good to know.
Now give me that cookie;
I discovered an element.
(Penny:)Thank you so much for coming.
(Raj:)You called the right person.
(Raj:)I believe I have the perfect romantic
evening for you to give Leonard.
(Penny:)Okay, good,
'cause I've been really struggling with this.
(Raj:)As I'm sure you're aware,
(Raj:)the quickest way to a man's heart
is through his...